>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们谈谈运动的第二部分。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's talk
about part two of the exercise.
所以如果我们从这个问题开始
So if we're starting from
this as our solution,
我们可以开始转换这些正则函数是声明或
we can start to convert these regular
functions that are declarations or
表达式为箭头函数。
expressions into arrow functions.
使用我们了解的各种错误函数语法。
Using the various things we know
about error functions syntax.
例如，可以将来自标识的学生创建为
So for example,
get students from ID could be created as
getStudentFromId ，并且将采用该方法。
getStudentFromId, and
it's gonna taken that.
它将返回学生的 studentRecords.find()，
And it's going to return
the student studentRecords.find(),
这是另一个函数表达式，我们想用一个箭头函数来做。
and here's another function expression
that we wanna do with an arrow function.
这就是我们的记录
So that one is record, and
那么这个表情。
then this expression.
这就是我们如何找到它的方法。
And that's how we find it.
这就是我们的定义
So, that's our definition for
与独立功能相比较的箭头函数。
the arrow function as compared
to the stand alone function.
我们会用打印记录来做同样的技术
We'll do the same technique
with print records.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And
rather than making a function block,
我可以看到这三种功能都是可以猜到的。
I can actually see that all three
of these functions are chainable.
由于排序将保留数组，并且数组将为局部数组，
Since sort will retain the array and
since the array will be a local array,
这个变异在这个特殊的情况下是不重要的
the mutation won't matter
in this particular case.
所以我就可以通过简单的说
So I can take advantage
of that by simply saying
recordeds.map(getStudentFromId) ，然后我可以说 .sort。
recordids.map(getStudentFromId), and
then I can say .sort.
在这里，我们还有一个功能，我们应该转换成一个数组函数。
And here, we have another function that
we should convert to an array function.
但这整个 If， thelse ， if thing as a th三元，所以
But this whole If, else,
if thing can be done as a ternary, so
我们不需要一个功能团体
we don't need a function body.
因此，让我们将它作为记录 d1 和 record2 中的箭头函数进行写入。
So let's write it as the arrow function
that takes in record1 and record2.
我们会使用三元，我将全部写在一行上，原因是为什么不这样做。
And we will use a ternary and I will
write it all on one line because why not.
开玩笑的你应该会笑的
That was a joke,
you were supposed to laugh at that.
Record1.name 小于 Record2.name ，然后返回 -1。
Record1.name is less than Record2.name,
then we return -1.
否则 (record1.name > record2.name)，
Otherwise (record1.name &gt; record2.name),
否则我们将返回 1 ，否则返回 0。
we return 1 otherwise 0.
这就是我们所谓的 " 错误 " 的功能。
So that's our error function
that we called the sort on.
然后我们再给他们打个电话
And then finally we call the .forEach,
and again,
我们有此功能正在接收记录和调用控制台日志。
we have this Function which is receiving
a record and calling console log.
由于控制台日志是函数调用，
Since console log is a function call,
它适合作为一种表达方式，意味着我们不需要一个箭头函数体。
it's suitable as an expression which means
we don't need an arrow function body.
所以我们可以简单地说记录然后调用 console.log
So we can simply say record and
then call the console.log,
既然我懒了我就把它复制了
and, since I'm lazy,
I'm just gonna copy it.
我不想再重新输入
I don't wanna retype it.
>> Kyle Simpson: 还有我们的箭头函数表示打印记录。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And there is our arrow
function representation of print records.
>> 凯尔辛普森: 助学生报名 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Paid students to enroll
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It
没有收到任何东西所以它是一个箭式功能
doesn't receive anything,
so it's an arrow function.
再次，我可以看到，我最终要做的是返回一个数组。
And again, I can see that what I'm
ultimately doing is returning an array.
所以我就可以简单的回到那个数组，然后
So I can just simply return that array,
and then have
包含在数组中通过链接将发生的内容。
Included in the array what's
going to happen through chaining.
所以，我要把这个表达出来。
So, that and
I'm going to spread out this expression.
此表达式将以 studentRecords.filter 开头，并且
And this expression will start
with studentRecords.filter and
这里是另一个可以是箭头函数的在线函数表达式。
here we are with another online function
expression that can be arrow function.
所以我会写一个箭头函数
So I'll write an arrow function.
从记录中开始我就会把它复制了
Takes in record and since I'm being lazy,
I'm gonna copy that.
那是我们的箭功能
There's our arrow function.
过滤后，我们可以简单地调用点映射，直接更改它。
After filter, we can simply call
the dot map, change directly off of it.
我们有另一个内联函数叫做 "获取学生 I-D " 。
We have another inline function called,
"Get student I-D".
它只返回记录。
It simply returns record.
这是每个人最喜欢的箭头函数。
This is everybody's favorite arrow
function which just does that.
然后这个阵列就会被传播出去
And that array then gets spread out.
是一份得到传播的 I-D 列表
It's a list of I-Ds that gets spread out
这个阵列是从付费学生回来的
into this array that's returned
from paid students to enroll.
这就是我们的箭功能。
So there is our arrow function.
>> Kyle Simpson: 现在，最后，提醒未付的是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And now,
finally, remind unpaid is
一个箭头函数，它使用记录标识和
an arrow function that
takes record IDs and
它是 recordIds.filter ，
it Does recordIds.filter, and
我们有一个学生标识箭头功能
we have a student ID arrow function or
参数称为 studentId 。
parameter called studentId that comes in.
我们可以再一次
And we can, again,
通过在函数调用中执行属性链，避免需要箭头块。
avoid needing an arrow block by doing
a property chain off the function call.
所以我们可以简单说， getStudentFromId(studentId)，
So we can simply say,
getStudentFromId(studentId),
然后从该调用中访问该属性，并将其求反。
and then access the property off
of that call, and negate it.
然后，我们可以调用 printRecords >> Kyle Simpson: 利用该输入。
And then, we can call printRecords
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: With that input.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此有一个箭头函数，而 yay!
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
there is that arrow function, and yay!
没有更多的常规函数，只有箭头函数。
No more regular functions,
only arrow functions.
>> Kyle Simpson: 有关第二部分练习的问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Any questions
about part two of the exercise?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes?
>> 扬声器 1: 具有多个三元作为回调函数的时刻，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: There was a moment with the
multiple ternary as the callback function,
链式阵列的方法，就像 - >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，
the chained array method, it's like-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah,
我把所有 [ CROSSTALK] >> 演讲者 1:
the one that I put all [CROSSTALK]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: I was like,
这肯定只是他在内部创造的一个修辞
surely that's just a rhetorical
gesture that he created inside.
然后我意识到，我两周前就写了类似的东西。
Then I realized, I had written
something like it two weeks ago.
我就像上帝
I was like, God.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我知道，我对那些喜欢
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I know,
my observation of those that like to
写箭头函数是有一种倾向
write arrow functions is that
there is a predisposition
尽可能使用最简洁的语法，
to use the most concise syntax possible,
你能用什么花招
using whatever tricks you possibly can.
包括嵌套在一起的内联系列，
Including Inline ternaries
that are nested together,
使用逗号运算符嵌套表达式。
using the comma operator
to nest expressions.
我见过人们在箭头中定义参数
I've seen people define
parameters in the arrow
参数列表是未使用的变量，因此
parameter list that
are unused variables so
它们不需要声明变量以在其表达式中使用。
that they don't have to declare a variable
to use inside of their expression.
我的意思是，任何一种语法的诡计，你都可以用一个简明的箭头
I mean, any sort of syntactic trick you
can use to get it down to a concise arrow
表达式似乎是正常的。
expression seems to be the norm.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，希望你现在感觉有点
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so hopefully
you now feel a little bit more with
一些更真实的世俗的代码
some slightly more real worldish code.
关于我们可以创建的函数之间的差异的一些想法
Some idea about the differences between
the functions that we can create as
声明，作为内联函数表达式，以及
declarations, as inline
function expressions, and
现在即使是箭头函数表达式。
now even as arrow function expressions.
您可以进行某些方面的比较。
You have some side by side
comparison that you can make.
您自己确定这些样式是否更便于阅读，
Make your own determinations on whether or
not these styles are more readable,
或者更能维护你的目的
or more maintainable, for your purpose.